(Howard:)I say we just take him
to Tatooine
(Howard:)and sell him to some Jawas.
(Raj:)That's two, dude.
(Raj:)Write your own jokes.
(Penny:)Oh, great.
(Penny:)Hi, I'm Penny,
I'll be your waitress.
(Leonard:)Why are you introducing
yourself?
(Penny:)I'd rather people not know
(Penny:)I have any prior connection
to you whatsoever.
(Sheldon-bot :)Can you tell me
the specials this evening?
(Penny:)Sheldon, I'm not waiting on you.
(Sheldon-bot:)Obviously.
(Sheldon-bot:)I don't even have
water yet.
(Penny:)Because you're not here.
(Sheldon-bot:)That's discrimination
against the otherwise located.
(Sheldon-bot:)I'm going to have
to go over your head.
(Sheldon-bot:)Manager... manager.
(Sheldon:)Oh, Lord,
look who it is.
(Howard:)Is that Steve Wozniak?
(Leonard:)I think it is.
(Sheldon-bot :)The Great and Powerful Woz.
(Howard(after Raj whispers to him):)Penny,
Steve Wozniak was
(Leonard:)one of the cofounders
(Leonard:)of Apple Computer.
(Leonard:)He and Steve Jobs started it...
Yeah,
I know who he is.
I watch Dancing with the Stars.